#### Contact

purva96d@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/purva-deshmukh-62b32517b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
C (Programming Language)
C++

### Certifications

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals

# Purva Deshmukh

Software Engineer at Shyena Tech Yarns Pvt Ltd | Python | Flask | Azure |

Pune

## Summary

I am a Self-taught Python Developer currently working at Shyena Tech Yarns. Pvt. Ltd., having 1.5 years of working experience in various technologies like Python, cloud computing(AWS, Azure), Flask, PostgreSQL. I have also worked on a few Machine learning and Deep learning projects using Tensorflow and python libraries like Numpy, Scikit learn.

## Experience

Honeywell Python Developer July 2019 - Present (1 year 9 months) Hadapsar

I currently work as a python developer at honeywell (client)

Shyena Tech Yarns Pvt Ltd Software Engineer March 2019 - July 2019 (5 months) karve nagar pune

### Education

Pune Institute of Computer Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical, Electronic and Communications

Engineering Technology/Technician · (2014 - 2018)